SHELDON:
I must say, Leonard...
...when I first heard your idea
for Giant Jenga I was skeptical.
I can't blame you,
Tiny Twister was a complete bust.
Oh. But I was wrong.
The looming threat of being crushed
under a pile of lumber...
...does add a certain spice.
I've never felt so alive.
[CHUCKLES]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Oh, hello, Alex. Let me go get you
last night's recordings.
What recordings?
Remember when you told me
I talk in my sleep?
It occurred to me that like most things I say,
it's probably pure gold.
So I started recording it all and...
...now Alex gets to comb through...
...eight hours of what I like to call
"Sheldon After Dark."
-Hey, Leonard.
-Hey.
Just playing a little Giant Jenga.
I know, I'm the one who
had to buy him the helmet.
So do you have plans this weekend?
Most of Saturday's gonna be figuring out
where to put this game when we're done.
How about you?
I'm gonna go hear Kip Thorne give a
lecture about subatomic space-time.
Oh, that's his take on John Wheeler's
quantum foam. That should be great.
Well, you can come with me.
I'd love to, but I'm supposed to
hang out with Penny.
-Well, bring her.
-Oh, she's not really into in that kind of stuff.
Well, if you want to hear about the lecture,
I can tell you all about it at work...
...or, you know, over dinner sometime.
What?
Giant Jenga! I win!
Oh, come on, that can't be true.
The Egg Salad Equivalency
I did the research. Tony the Tiger...
...Dig 'Em the frog, Cap'N Crunch, Toucan
Sam, Count Chocula, Trix the Rabbit...
...Snap, Crackle and Pop.
Not one cereal mascot is a girl.
It's a total breakfast sausage fest.
Are we done with this?
Almost. Franken Berry, Boo Berry,
Sugar Bear, and the Honey Nut Cheerio Bee.
I believe his name is Buzz.
Terrific. Something weird happened
and I don't know what to do about it.
-What's going on?
-Sheldon's assistant...
...asked me on a date.
How could you do that to me?
You know I've been working it
with Alex for weeks.
Working it? You can't even talk to her.
I talk with my eyes.
You look like my little cousin when
he's dropping one in his diaper.
She knows I have a girlfriend.
It's so weird.
Oh, my God. You're loving this!
To my bones.
[CHUCKLING]
I'm not gonna do anything about it.
I love Penny.
It's just nice to have a young, attractive
woman sniffing around the goods.
I both hate you and want to be you.
This is Ryan Gosling all over again.
Aww. Gentlemen. What is on the
conversational menu this morning?
Leonard stole my woman,
and he knew...
...I was only six to eight months away
from making my move.
I didn't steal anyone.
Your assistant is totally hitting on this jerk
and he loves it.
Well, that's not acceptable. I'm her boss.
She needs to be solely focused
on my needs...
...not distracted by your pasty,
androgynous brand of sexuality.
I'm androgynous?
Oh, please. Look at you with your
pouty bee-stung lips.
What do you think I should do?
I say you tell Alex your heart
belongs to Penny.
I provide her a shoulder to cry on,
then roughly half a year later...
...I give it to her good.
I want to thank you all for coming on such
short notice. In the past...
...I've reached out to each of you
individually...
...but I believe my present situation
requires the collective wisdom of the group.
Which, as you can see from
your commemorative t-shirts, I've dubbed...
...Sheldon Cooper's Council of Ladies.
What is happening?
I need your advice about a delicate
workplace situation.
To protect those involved,
I'll be changing their names.
Who's involved?
A short, bespectacled colleague of mine...
...who lives in the shadow
of his brilliant roommate.
Uh.... Let's call this colleague
Ricardo Shilly-Shally.
-You're talking about Leonard.
-No, no.
Shilly-Shally has red hair and
briefly served in the Mexican Navy.
Anyway, despite the fact
that he has a girlfriend...
...Shilly-Shally has been the recipient...
...of inappropriate workplace flirtations
from a young lady.
-It's your assistant Alex, isn't it?
-No.
No, it's Tondelaya della Ventimiglia.
What the hell is going on
with Leonard and Alex?
I'm sorry, who's talking about
Leonard and Alex?
Fine. Ricardo and Tondelaya.
It's not really about
Ricardo and Tondelaya.
It is really about her boss...
...who doesn't quite know how to handle
this situation and could use your advice...
...which is surprising, because
Dr. Einstein Von Brainstorm...
...he's usually pretty smart
about these things.
Ugh. I'm gonna kill her!
You've got nothing to worry about.
Leonard would never cheat on you.
She's right. But say the word, I got a lab
full of cocaine-addicted monkeys...
...with nothing to lose.
One of them could end up
in the back seat of her car.
Or her shower.
Ladies, ladies, please.
We're not here to talk about Penny.
We're here to talk about me.
I mean Einstein Von Brainstorm! Darn it.
All right, I guess the cat's out of the bag.
Let me explain what's going on.
Ricardo is really Leon--
We know what's going on, Sheldon!
But what should I do?
Alex is your employee.
If she's doing something that's...
...making Leonard uncomfortable,
you should talk to her.
Oh, he's not uncomfortable at all.
He's loving it.
He's strutting around
like he's 5-foot-6.
What? He's loving it?
Sheldon, you need to talk to Alex
right away.
Talk to her. That's all you've got?
With a cool name like
Sheldon Cooper's Council of Ladies...
...I really expected more.
Give me back the t-shirts.
Alex, check my schedule.
What does my afternoon look like?
I think it's pretty wide open. Oh, wait.
Here's something at 4:00.
"Give Alex a talking to"?
Well, that snuck up on us, didn't it?
-Is there a problem?
-Let's not call it a problem...
...let's call it an opportunity.
To solve a serious problem.
What did I do?
You don't know? Oh, you poor dear.
Your ovaries are squirting so much
goofy juice into your brain...
...you don't know which way is up.
You made an inappropriate
sexual advance towards Dr. Hofstadter.
What? I didn't make a sexual advance
on anybody.
Now, there's no need to get defensive.
I'm not unsympathetic to your plight.
My father used to say
that a woman is like...
...an egg salad sandwich
on a warm Texas day.
What?
Full of eggs and only appealing
for a short time.
This conversation
is making me uncomfortable.
Yeah, you and me both, sister.
Please understand, I don't hold you
responsible for your behavior.
From an evolutionary standpoint,
you're a slave to your desire to reproduce.
But during the work day...
...when you feel possessed
by amorous intent, may I suggest...
...you suppress it by leafing through
this illustrated book...
...of sexually transmitted diseases.
[SHELDON SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, yes. Check out this oozy doozy.
I have to go.
So does this fellow, but he
can't without it burning like hot soup.
[LEONARD WHISTLING]
Hey, pretty lady.
You seem extra happy.
-I guess I am.
-Any particular reason why?
No, just having a good day.
This morning Sheldon fell asleep
on the way to work...
...so I got to listen to the radio.
That was crazy.
Mm-hm. Anything else?
Mm.... I found this quiz online called
"Which Star Trek Character Are You?"
It only took me four tries
to get Captain Kirk. Heh.
-That's great.
-Oh.
[MIMICS CAPTAIN KIRK]
It. Was.
[GIGGLES]
Hmm.
I'm glad you're having such a great day.
And the one thing that could make it
better is an evening with my special girl.
Oh, and who's that?
What do you mean?
I just didn't know if you meant me
or Alex.
Why would I mean Alex?
Because I know she hit on you
and I know you liked it!
[NERVOUSLY]
What?
Don't play dumb with me,
Ricardo Shilly-Shally!
I'm missing something.
Did you say something to Penny
about Alex?
Yes, and a fat lot of good it did me.
All she did was get mad at you.
Why would you do that?
I needed advice about a woman.
I would have asked you, but
if the last few years have proven anything...
...it's that you can't tell a uterus
from a unicycle.
At least I know not to blab to a girl
about somebody flirting with her boyfriend.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Good to know.
A few more helpful hints like that...
...you may find yourself
on the Council of Ladies.
Hello?
I see. What time?
Very well, then.
Huh. That was the Human Resources
Department at the university.
Apparently my assistant, Alex,
has filed a complaint accusing me of...
...inappropriate behavior
in the workplace.
Oh, my God. What did you do?
Oh. Let me think....
Nothing, I'm a delight.
Human Resources Department.
Come in?
-Hello.
-Ah. Dr. Cooper, have a seat.
Thank you.
I called you in today because
your assistant...
...Alex Jensen has
lodged a complaint against you.
So I've been told. But I can't understand
what she has to complain about.
She has a front row seat as I
make scientific history...
...there's string cheese in my mini-fridge
and that's for anyone...
...and just yesterday I led her away
from a life of sexual promiscuity...
...by making her look at pictures
of disease-ridden genitalia.
Cancel my next appointment.
This is gonna take a while.
Dr. Cooper, you said things
to your employee...
...that you just cannot say
in the workplace.
Like what?
Well, according to Ms. Jensen you said...
...that she was a
"slave to her biological urges"...
...and called her an "egg salad sandwich."
I don't even know what that means...
...but I'm gonna go ahead
and tell you you can't say it.
Oh, I see the confusion here.
Alex thought I was singling her out. No.
I meant that all women
are slaves to their biological urges.
Even you.
You're a slave.
I'm a what?
I'm just saying. At a certain point
in a woman's menstrual cycle--
Uh-uh. Oh.
You can't talk about that either.
Your language is entirely inappropriate,
and I'm going to advise...
...that you shut your mouth right now.
I don't see why I'm the one being
persecuted here.
Dr. Hofstadter was bragging about his
sexual desirability...
...to anyone who would listen.
Howard Wolowitz spent two years
using university resources...
...building a six-breasted sex robot.
And at the office Christmas party,
I heard Rajesh Koothrappali...
...refer to you several times
as "Brown Sugar."
Hofstadter, Wolowitz and
that last one was Rajesh Koothrappali?
Yes. But in his defense,
that wasn't racist. He's also brown.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[SINGING]
I'm sorry Alex hit on me
Hit on me, hit on me
Sorry Alex hit on me
I had no idea I'm cute
Aw. Damn it, you are.
[CHUCKLES]
Please forgive me,
I should have told you about Alex.
I don't care about Alex. Fine, I care.
Okay, I hate the bitch.
But what really hurt
is that you liked it so much.
Do I need to be worried?
Of course not. No. Why?
Because she's pretty and smart
and when you talk about work...
...she doesn't have to look up words
in the dictionary...
...to understand what you said.
-You do that?
-No.
Hang on. Are you feeling insecure?
Because that's my thing.
And if you take it away, I don't know
what I'm bringing to this relationship.
Yes, Leonard, I am insecure. Happy?
No, I'm not happy.
Why are you smiling?
I'm sorry, it's just I never think of you
having feelings like that.
-Well, I do.
-Why?
Nothing is ever going to happen
between me and Alex.
Good.
Come here.
-Can I tell you a secret?
-What's that?
With all these women chasing me,
I kind of do feel like Captain Kirk.
-Can I tell you a secret?
-Sure.
Keep talking about Captain Kirk
and we're all gonna stop.
[MIMICS CAPTAIN KIRK]
Message. Received.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Excuse me.
Hello.
This is Dr. Hofstadter.
Okay.
All right, thank you.
That's weird.
I'm getting called into Human Resources.
What did you do?
I don't know.
Huh. I just got called into Human Resources.
Why?
I don't know. Heh.
Huh. That is so strange. Human Resources
wants to talk to me tomorrow.
Could you stop licking your ass
for two minutes? I have a problem here.
Do you really think
you should be drinking right now?
How else am I supposed to talk
to the human resources lady?
I don't know, seek professional help?
I did. The guy at the liquor store said
this stuff tastes great in coffee.
You got called in too? What is going on?
Sheldon threw us all under the bus.
I feel like I've been called
to the principal's office.
Although I wouldn't mind
if Brown Sugar suspended me...
...from a sex swing. Heh.
This may have been a mistake.
Relax, everything's gonna be fine.
Before I met Bernadette,
I was in here every other day.
Little tip, turn off your "I Like Big Butts"
ringtone before you go in.
-This is all your fault.
-How is this my fault?
If you weren't screwing around
with Sheldon's assistant...
-...this wouldn't have happened.
-I wasn't screwing around.
Oh, of course not, she was just
sniffing around your goods...
...because she was hunting for truffles.
Ah. Mr. Wolowitz, it's been a while.
Hey, Janine. Heh. How're Tom and the kids?
Fine.
You must be Dr. Hofstadter?
Yes, but I think this is all
a big misunderstanding.
Yeah, me too. I didn't do anything.
Is that alcohol on your breath?
Howard built a sex robot.
That is not true.
All I did was build a robot.
Did it have six breasts?
I'm sorry, I'm a feminist. Heh.
I don't notice things like...
...how many breasts a robot has.
Well, hello.
What are you doing here?
-Actually, I came to speak to Mrs. Davis.
-And I'm a little busy right now.
But I came to file a complaint. Somebody
has made me feel uncomfortable...
...in the workplace by using language
of an inappropriate and sexual nature.
-And who is that?
-You, you dirty birdy.
I thought about the things
you said yesterday...
...and I realized I'm deeply offended.
Now, be a dear and get me
one of those complaint forms.
That's it. All of you, in my office now.
Thanks to you, I know better
than to ask if you're menstruating.
Based on your behavior, I don't have to.
It has been pointed out to me that
some of the things I said to you...
...could be construed as offensive.
And I would like to offer you
my sincerest apology.
Thank you, Dr. Cooper.
Additionally, you should know
that the university has mandated...
...that I take an online sexual harassment
seminar so that this sort of thing...
...doesn't happen in the future.
-Okay.
-Now, unfortunately...
...my time is much too valuable
to waste on nonsense like this...
...so I'm going to need you
to take it for me.
Oh, and you'd better ace it,
they're pretty mad.
-I was thinking about that stuff with Alex--
-Would you stop worrying about that?
I can't help it. But I figured
I could sit around...
...and feel insecure, or
I could do something about it.
So, I got a course catalog at school
and looked at some of the science classes.
-That's great.
-No, it isn't...
...they are extremely boring, how do you
not kill yourself, like, every day?
Anyway, I decided I don't need to be
a scientist, I could just look like one.
So I bought these.
Glasses? I really don't think
that's gonna change--
Oh, my God, you look so smart and hot!
I know, right? Watch this.
Molecules.
-Okay, come with me.
-Where are we going?
To my bedroom so I can take everything off
but those glasses.
And maybe the boots.